the nourish nutrition scale was designed
to give you deeper insight into your
meals the built-in database can
reference thousands of foods simply
match your food to its code and wet
along with weight the scale will display
calories fat sugar and more its
beautiful glass surface means effortless
cleaning and the low profile design
makes storage a breeze hi I'm Nick
an erotic specialist you can contact me
before or after your purchase with any
questions you might have and with our
robust paperless manuals you can learn
the ins and outs of our products at any
time be sure to check out the rest of
our content to learn how greater goods
is striving to make things better